<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<data>
<template id="report_application_request">
    <t  t-call="web.html_container">
        <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
          <t t-call="web.external_layout">
            <h2>Application Request</h2>

            <t t-if="doc.state in ['draft','in_progress','hr_approval']">

                Date : <t t-esc="datetime.datetime.now().strftime('%Y-%m-%d')" t-options="{'widget': 'date'}" class="m-0"/>
                <p>Subject : Promotion Request</p>
                <p>From: <t t-esc="doc.employee_id.name" /></p>
                <p>To: <t t-esc="doc.employee_parent_id.name" /></p>

                <p>I would like to bring to your notice that I have been working at your firm for the past <t t-esc="doc.period" /> years as the <t t-esc="doc.job_title" /> in <t t-esc="doc.department_id.name" /> Department. 
                During this time, I have worked earnestly and passionately for achieving the highest profits for our firm. </p>
                <br/>
                <p>With all the knowledge, experience, and know-how-of how things work here at <t t-esc="doc.company_id.name" />, I request you to kindly promote me to the position of <t t-esc="doc.requested_position.name" /> in <t t-esc="doc.department_id.name" /> Department.
                I assure you, I completely understand the responsibilities with this post and I promise that I will prove to be the righteous choice for our firm.</p>


                <p>Looking forward to a positive response!</p>
                <p>Thanking you in anticipation.</p>

            </t>
            <t t-if="doc.state=='manager_approval'">

                Date : <t t-esc="datetime.datetime.now().strftime('%Y-%m-%d')" t-options="{'widget': 'date'}" class="m-0"/>
                <p>Subject : Promotion Request</p>
                <p>From: <t t-esc="doc.employee_id.name" /></p>
                <p>To: <t t-esc="doc.employee_parent_id.name" /></p>

                <p>Good Day!</p>
                <br/>

                <p>
                On behalf of the management, i congratulate you on your performance for tis year. Your performance and the attached resume clearly speaks for itself and the whole board acknowledges the contributions you have made this year. 
                They have anonimously voted to approve your promotion request to the position of <t t-esc="doc.requested_position.name" /> in <t t-esc="doc.department_id.name" /> Department.
                </p>

                <br/>

                <p>Managment is expecting good things and more contribution from you. We believe you have what it takes to take the challenges of this new job and bring about a great success to the business. </p>
            </t>

            <t t-if="doc.state=='rejected'">

                Date : <t t-esc="datetime.datetime.now().strftime('%Y-%m-%d')" t-options="{'widget': 'date'}" class="m-0"/>
                <p>Subject : Promotion Request</p>
                <p>From: <t t-esc="doc.employee_id.name" /></p>
                <p>To: <t t-esc="doc.employee_parent_id.name" /></p>

                <p>Good Day!</p>
                <br/>

                <p>
                Thank you for throwing your hat into the ring for the promotion to <t t-esc="doc.requested_position.name" />. I wanted to let you know that we've decided to offer the position to another colleague/new hire.

While your work and dedication are appreciated,Please keep up the good work and don't lose your competitive spirit. I expect that more opportunities will come up.
</p>

                <br/>

             </t>
            

        </t>
    </t>
    </t>
</template>
</data>
</odoo>
